#### **OTIS ALEXANDER ADDO-EGYIR**

Address: P.O.Box CO1, Tema Community 1

Telephone: +233 057 382 0770
Email: alexanderegyir@gmail.com

Date of Birth: 25<sup>th</sup> April, 1993 Place of Birth: Sekondi

Country of Citizenship: Ghana Country of Residence: Ghana

**Objectives:** To have an international cultural exposure and hands-on experience in the field of Administration especially in non-profit management. To develop my management skills and become globally competitive.

#### **Education:**

Institution name:	Duration:
Our Lady of Mercy Senior High School (WASSCE)	2010-2013
University of Ghana (Bachelors Degree in Administration)	2013-2017

# Relevant work experience:

Position	Institution	Duration
1. Production Assistant	Technoplast Industries Ltd	May- August 2010
2. Census Taker	AC Nielson	March- June 2014
3. Volunteer	Nasco Foundation	May 2015 till date
4. Marketing Ambassador	Stanbic Bank	February- April 2016
5. Verification Officer	Electoral Commission of Ghana	2016-2017
<b>6.</b> Administrative Assistant	University of Ghana	Sept 2017 till date

# **Skills/Qualification:**

Language: Proficient in English

Computer Skills: Intermediate Certificate in Microsoft Word, Excel and PowerPoint

Leadership: Head of Welfare Committee, UG-DE SRC

# **Activities and Interest:**

Reading, online research and Gymnastics